rentasmile.com 2012-04-05

# Personal Assistance | Concierge Services | Virtual Administration | Privacy Policy: Virtual Assistance | Outsourcing Company

Rent A Smile lays a great emphasis to your privacy. The key to the success of our business is maintaining the trust of our users, and this Privacy Policy is intended to make you feel as comfortable as possible for visiting our website and using our services thereof. Rent A Smile respects your privacy and recognizes the need to protect the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number) you share with us. We would like to assure you that we follow appropriate standards when it comes to protecting your privacy on our web sites This Privacy Policy elucidates the privacy practices for the concierge services, web sites and any other sites and services operated by Rent A Smile. This Privacy Policy will provide you with information on varied aspects such as : 

* We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and/or to administer our Web site. This gives us an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user’s session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous. 

* You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. However, our Web site may at various occasions require you to give us contact information like your name and email address and other personal information. We use the contact information only to respond to your queries or send you information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by choosing request the same to us by return mail. We may use your personal information to make this Web Site more relevant for your needs and create and publish content that may be useful to you. 

* We occasionally engage other parties to provide limited services to us or on our behalf. We will only provide those other parties the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

* Rent A Smile may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Rent A Smile or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Rent A Smile and its family of Websites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Rent A Smile employees, users of Rent A Smile’s products or services, or members of the public. 

* Your information may be stored and processed in any other country in which Rent A Smile or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

* Rent A Smile takes precautions to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, the same is protected both online and off-line. When our registration and personal profile forms prompts the users to enter sensitive information, that information is protected using industry-standard SSL encryption. 

We hope this policy clarifies our procedures regarding your Personal Information. We will notify you by e-mail of any significant changes and obtain your “opt-in” consent to any significant new uses of your Personal Information, if it was collected from you prior to a significant change in this policy. We may also make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that generally will not affect our use of your Personal Information. You provide certain information to us that are personal in nature, when you: 

(a)Register to use the services 

(b) Register for free newsletters 

(c) Complete questionnaires 

(d) Order products and services from us 

(e) Register to be notified of changes in our website 

(f) Send e-mail messages, submit forms or send other information to us 

When you give us personal information, Rent A Smile will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. 

* When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the user’s machine (if the user accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above. 

* If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from Rent A Smile, you will be able to view the text on the screens; however, you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site. 

* This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and/or alteration of information under our control. The data resides behind a firewall, with access restricted to authorize Rent A Smile personnel. 

* This site may contain links to other sites. Rent A Smile is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Websites. 

* Rent A Smile will occasionally update this privacy statement.
